IGOR PAPRZYCKI



PHONE

+48 504 781 817

EMAIL

igypap@gmail.com

GITHUB

ADDRESS

Jana Kazimierza 11B/91 01-248 Warszawa POLAND

Summary

Ambitious, highly skilled professional with four years of experience in aviation industry as process automation engineer. Possess strong software skills in Java, C++, LabVIEW & PLC. Have a depth analytical and problem-solving skills combined with passion and commitment to software engineering.

Technical skills

JAVA 8 KNOWLEDGE

- OOP
- Design Patterns (DAO, MVC)
- Interfaces
- Collections
- Polymorphism
- Enums

BASIC KNOWLEDGE

- SpringBoot, Thymeleaf
- SQLite, MSSQL, SQLServer,
 Hibernate
- JUnit
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, jQuery
- Android (XML, ButterKnife, Activity Lifecycle)

DEV TOOLS

- Intellij IDEA
- GIT
- Maven, Gradle
- Android Studio

Projects

TODO List

Android app for managing tasks, with menu, ORMLite database, RecyclerView and notifications. It works in vertical and horizontal position.

Pocket

Android Pocket app for storing website links and telephone contacts. It allows to open website in a browser, send sms or call. It works in vertical and horizontal position.

Kwejk

SpringBoot & Thymeleaf web application to share gifs. Hibernate and MySQL technologies used to store gif data.

Courses

JAVA Bootcamp october 2016 - MARCH 2017

AkademiaKodu.pl

Java BootCamp programming course for Android and Spring web application development.

Quiz

Quiz application for Android - display questions, 3 answers and show the results at the end. It works in vertical and horizontal position.

Experience

Goldman Sachs JUNE 2017 - present

Junior JAVA Developer

Software development for banking and financial industry.

Technologies: JAVA 8, Spring, JMS, IntelliJ, Gradle, SVN

Freelancer APRIL 2016 - OCTOBER 2016

C++/QT Developer

The project deliverable was to develop GUI application providing MODBUS communication with industrial PLC controller & Ethernet IDS camera.

Application main tasks: calibration parameters settings, data acquisition, image capture, data analysis & report generation.

Technologies used: Qt Framework, MODBUS TCP/IP, multithreading, OpenCV library, STL containers.

Institute of Aviation JANUARY 2013 - MAY 2017

ENGINEER

Aviation engines Fan Blade Out facility design and commissioning. The Warsaw Institute of Aviation center can now boast of having the world's largest vacuum chamber. Designed for Fan Blade detachment tests in largest turbine engines. It is 12 meters long, it has 5.5 meters in internal diameter and weighs 177 tons.

My responsibilities: Data Acquisition, sensor instrumentation & HMI systems design and commissioning. Works mainly with National Instruments hardware and LabVIEW software.

Education

Kielce University of Technology 2011 - 2012

MASTER OF SCIENCE (M. Sc.), Electrical Engineering

Graduation in 5% of the best University students.

Kielce University of Technology 2007 - 2011

FIRST DEGREE ENGINEER, Electrical Engineering